Instead of using the art node, the steel bit or something, this was known to all the
analyst who is working on the shift, because it was known to for a blue team who are in
the investigation.
So, let us think about the different ways, that the attack will be also using black
base, black base load for an exfiltration, so many of them does not know what is the black
base, it is an cloud storage, black base load, so this black base load storage will be
supporting all of an executable called B2.exe, so us like oneDrive.exe, oneDrive.exe
will be uploading help us to uploading files into the cloud storage oneDrive, the similar
to the oneDrive, there is a B2.exe for a black base, the threat factors will be also using
this black base to deliver to achieve the exfiltration that they will be uploading their files
to, they will be uploading their files to the cloud platform, black base, okay.
So, we have seen this scenario multiple times, so here you can see B2.exe and it was
seeking to different direct rates inside the black base load, so how we discussed about the
wind rare in the collection section, how we discussed about the arc on the exfiltration
section, the commands will be more and more similar, you can understand this command,
they will be targeting the Excel document or later applications and they will be uploading
the data into the B2.exe, okay. So here you can see the command S5 CMD.exe for our
exfiltration, so also we have noticed B2.exe, B2.exe, public platforms or some kind
of Firefox, okay. So we noticed this kind of scenario a lot of times, so you need to be
aware about, they can use, they can widely used any tools for an expert, any cloud
uploading tools for an exfiltration, not only the arc run or omega or ultrive or the
known application, they can use set of application, we have a lot of applications to supporting
cloud storage, they need to think about that, because the threat type doesn't be thinking
they think like a real user, the legitimate user and they will be moving the data to the
backup, we will be thinking the user moving to the data to the backup, but the background
scenario, the threat type will be accelerating a lot of files from the machine, more than
like 2,200 GB, 500 GB plus data, okay. So this will be really, really important, we
need to think out of the box and we need to understand what was happening, so what about
the applications and all the way you are investigation, okay. Let's hop off from here, we'll
continue our discussion in our next review.
See you guys, bye bye.